Tomasz Bizoza

Phone: (+48) 53 53 33 292

E-mail: tombrzoza50@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/tombrzo

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomasz-brzoza-245399175/

www: https://portfolio-35a24.firebaseapp.com/

For many years I used to work in the tourism industry organizing business trips and flights. I've worked with people for people.

Nowadays my main professional goal is to find a job that will give me an opportunity to deepen and improve my programming skills, engage in interesting and creative projects and raise my Front-End development qualifications.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Git
- Customer needs identification
- Responding to customer concerns



Projects

• **Portfolio** single page application based on React Router

• Facebook - Clone single page application based on React Router

• Places to go single page application based on React Router

Weather App based on JavaScript, CSS

AppLab landing page based on JavaScript, SCSS

Notify landing page based on HTML and CSS

Education

1988-10 1993-06 Adam Mickiewicz University in Poznań

Institute of Anthropology and Ethnology

Experience

2007-08 - 2020-09 Travel Consultant, Weco Travel Sp. z o.o., Rainbow Tours S.A., Poznań

- customer service
- preparing commercial offers
- making reservations and selling airline tickets

2006-01 - 2007-07 Travel Consultant, Exodus Travels Ltd., London

- making reservations and selling airline tickets
- customer service

1994-08 - 2005-12 Travel Consultant, Blue Sky Travel, Fantur s.c., Poznań

- making reservations and selling airline tickets
- customer service